THANKS for the other authors and Sprite Makers
==============================================================================================

A big thanks to Mr. lord-master from the deviantart sprite the source of my first character.
also, a big thank you to Mr. Wou for the movesets and animations pattern.

with your help, I would not have much dedication in creating this character. and also Capcom for the inclusion of this character in the Resident Evil franchise.

for all the sprite makers and M.U.G.E.N lovers, 
I appeal to other sprite makers to continue and love 2D sprite and animation making.

characters planned this month and for next year.

Flik (Suikoden series)
Tina Armstrong (DOA series)
Talim (Soul Calibur series)

and more...